In the last 10 years violence in Mexico caused 160,000 deaths and more than 53,000 disappeared .
Entire areas of some cities are being deserted .
C 'mon , those who have not participated .
There are no figures for children that the dead and the disappeared have left behind .
Now silence , Ana , please .
Let 's see today the elements that appear in fairy tales .
Who can tell me , for instance , what characters normally appear in fairy tales .
- Fairies . - Princes .
Princes , of course .
- Three wishes ! - Yes , there are always three wishes . Very good .
- Foxes . - Witches . - Specters .
- What else ? - Vampires . - Very good .
- Tigers . - Tigers , very good .
Well , now with all those elements we 're going to write a story .
And with those characters .
C 'mon , c 'mon , now , silence .
Concentrate . Don 't talk .
C 'mon , quiet , each one to his story .
Don 't copy , either .
There was once a prince who wanted to be a tiger .
Tigers never forget .
They are hunters .
Their eyes see in the darkness .
They have fangs to break bones .
Tigers are not afraid .
- Now , asshole , you 're going to give it to me . - Wait , Caco . Caco !
What , baldy ? Go to hell .
Caco , where are you going ?
What the fuck , asshole ? I already told you that I 'm staying , your fucking mother .
I 'm staying . Leave me alone , kid .
It 's four in the morning . Calm down .
Leave me alone , asshole .
C 'mon , fucking Caco .
But the prince couldn 't be a tiger
because he had forgotten how to be a prince .
We forget that we are princes ,
warriors ,
tigers ,
when things from outside come to get us .
On the ground , on the ground !
All duck .
Estrella .
Here .
Three wishes .
As in fairy tales .
Everything will be fine , children .
C 'mon , children .
Let 's continue doing our lists .
Classes suspended until further notice . The principal .
We forget who we are
when things from outside come to get us .
THEY RETURN
Mom .
I arrived , mom .
Servando Esparza is the candidate that carries the voice of this nation .
Mom , they closed the school .
No classes .
Mom .
Servando Esparza is one of us , he 's a citizen like you and me .
For all that , these upcoming elections vote for Chino .
Tiger without kicks .
- Don 't push me down . - We are fighting . Do you want me to kill you ?
No , no .
Heck .
- C 'mon . - I 'll grab my lamp myself . Why do you grab it ?
What do you want , Morro ?
The tiger ?
Hey , Shine , he asks for you to tell him the story of the tiger again .
Don 't wet your pants , Morro .
Then you don 't sleep , mate .
Wait . Here .
Now it 's wrecked .
There was a very rich man
who had many wild animals .
He had tigers , lions , cougars , panthers , jaguars .
One day the Guascas arrived and killed him .
Caco and the other Guascas killed all the animals ,
but when they got to the tiger 's cage , he had escaped .
And now he walks around all the streets , angry and hungry .
He eats dogs , cats ,
and children with not parents .
And that 's it .
Hey , this kid !
Well , let 's go on .
Welcome to voicemail . Leave a message after the tones .
Hurry up , Morro , don 't fool around or we 'll leave you !
Mom , where are you ?
I 'm hungry .
Talk to me , please .
I 'm a princess ?
No , you are a warrior .
And then ?
And the spell was broke .
- And the prince was again a prince . - And then ?
And then nothing . You must go to bed because you have school tomorrow .
Let 's go to sleep , yes , yes .
No !
Now , time to go to bed .
Mom , mom .
When are you going to give me your little birds bracelet ?
When you get big
and I 'm gone .
I want my mom to come back .
Estrella .
Mom ?
I 'm here .
Heck , are you still here ?
- She 's not here . - Yes she is .
She 's not , cowgirl ! She 's not !
It belongs to my mom .
What do you want ?
She doesn 't need this anymore . In addition , the Guascas already took her away .
It 's not true ! My mom came back yesterday !
Estrella .
Go away .
DISAPPEARED
Is this the house ? - Yes , yes , up there .
- There , go . It 's in place . - No . Take it further back .
- Now it 's in place , right ? - Let 's go at once .
Shine , the boss .
That movie is so hideous .
They are so bloody .
It 's so dreadful .
Pure death .
You brought some good things .
They are cool , huh ?
- Beans . - Yuck .
Where did you steal , or where did you get in ?
You even brought the cell phones .
- So you see . - And who will you call , if we have nobody ?
I 'll call you all , mate .
These are for you . There , hand them around .
An identical one ? What do you want it for ?
You should have sold that with the dragon .
This is not to sell , asshole .
Come on , give me that one .
What are you doing ? Why do you put off the peas ?
Tell him . Tell him , Shine .
Yeah , eat those peas .
I don 't like peas .
Eat them , they are your vegetables .
Fuck !
- Who 's this ? - She got stuck to me .
- Where ? - To my buttocks .
I 'm hungry .
Wait .
We don 't fucking care if you 're hungry or not . Right , Pop ?
Yes , you mean nothing to them , and I hope the tiger eats you . Not me , Tucsy .
The tiger eats meat .
A lot .
Show him , Morro .
Goodbye , cowgirl .
No , please no ! Don 't take me to the house !
- Leave her , Shine . Leave her . - Don 't take me to my house !
Let her stay .
The Guascas are going to grab her . She will not last long .
They will take her to Chino , she 's doomed .
She 's a female .
Girls are bad luck .
Cover it , cover there .
Morro , do something , mate .
Stop eating , asshole .
- Thank you . - Shh ! - Morro ! What did I say ?
Mom ?
What 's up ?
The Guascas ?
No .
If you wake me up again , I 'm going to punch you twice !
Cowgirl , there come the Guascas !
You go the other way !
Shine !
Move it !
C 'mon !
I 'm going to kill you , son of a bitch !
That 's my gun , asshole !
- Let 's go , Shine ! - Where did you find it , you bastard ?
- Let 's move on ! - You grabbed the phone , bastard ?
You 're going to return my phone , son of your fucking mother !
- Shine ! - Shine !
- Where 's Morro ? - They took Morro , mate .
They grabbed him by the leg . He was running and they grabbed him .
And shots , and shots .
He threw the stuffed animal , mate . They took him .
What do they do to those they take away ?
They are caught . They take them to Chino . Chino makes them into pieces . They sell their parts .
They are satanic drug traffickers , they have a pact with the devil .
They even do red masses .
- They are black . - Red or black , whatever .
The ladies are killed . The cowboys - here , look at me - -
they take the cowboys away to who knows where .
And you know why they caught Morro ?
Because of YOU .
Because of you , you 're the cause they caught Morro ,
because they found out that there was a toddler girl with us .
- It 's not true . - No , it was your fault .
I know how I can disappear that Guasca .
Go and kill him .
If you want , we 'll take you to his house .
And if you kill him , you can stay with us .
- How do I get in ? - You jump in .
You knock .
And you kill him .
No , better not .
That bastard killed your mom .
Also yours .
Kill him yourself . You are a man .
That 's true , Shine .
Well , if you don 't kill him and become a man
tomorrow he will go out again and he will grab you , he will look for you .
He will cut you into pieces and eat you in a black mass .
- Or red . - Whatever fucking color it is .
You got it , cowgirl ?
If you don 't kill him , they 're going to kill us all .
- Go , go . - C 'mon . C 'mon .
Hurry up . C 'mon .
Hurry up .
Hurry up . Hurry up , c 'mon .
The sociologist Marant Ruiz Martínez talking about the candidacy
of Servando Esparza who is running for the Social Move party .
He 's also known by the nickname " Chino " .
We will receive him next .
The important thing is to get the following message that I will highlight to the media .
This , in order to defuse the political campaign of Mr. Servando Esparsa ,
better known as " Chino " , candidate of the Social Move party .
This man has direct links with organized crime ,
particularly with the band of the Guascas .
Severando Esparza , better known as " Chino "
has directly participated in human trafficking :
prostitution , torture , multiple murders ,
in addition to the links he has with drug trafficking .
I wish I don 't have to kill him .
Come , come .
Morro ! Morro !
I thought we would never see you again .
Gee , handsome one , you 're fine !
You 're good !
And there lies Caco , eating !
And suddenly Estrella takes out the gun ,
aims at Caco ...
" No , cowgirl , no , please don 't kill me ! "
" Nevermore I 'll eat children of the ... "
Pam ! She kills him .
You won 't eat pizza anymore .
How did you do to kill him ?
I lost a wish .
If I had had wishes I would have killed him ,
but since I don 't have ...
Are you angry ?
Is that the phone Caco wanted ?
Why do you keep it ?
Tucsy 's granny died of a bullet in a burial .
Pop 's brothers helped them a lot .
This Morro , they say he was able to speak before .
Maybe some day he saw something ugly .
It was all because of that bastard and his fucking brothers .
But Caco no longer ...
Come .
And that 's how Estrella dances .
And that 's how Morro dances with Rodrigo , and Pop .
Estrella .
They will come for you .
For killing him .
I did 't kill him .
No .
The one who killed him is looking for you .
And he will find you .
You have to bring him .
What 's up ?
Estrella says that we should get a cooler house .
Where each one of us has a room of his own ,
where we have videogames and a soccer field , a zoo ,
and several things like that , and even a pool .
- Of course not . - Well , I 'd be cool .
Shut up now , you bastards . And calm down .
This is my house and here I command .
And besides , there are no houses with soccer fields , or those stupid things .
I told you .
The Guascas know where we are .
And one of them was already killed .
You killed him .
That 's why we have to leave .
Stop it , Morro . Grab that box , mate .
What about those ?
Stand up , Pop , we have to do something .
You look like a little princess .
Wrecked bastards .
Shine .
Still angry ?
What 's with you ?
And now what 's with him ?
He 's crying because he misses his brother a lot .
He belongs to Brian 's gang .
Fuck him .
No , because as Estrella killed Caco
they are afraid to stay alone .
And , here is your asshole to take you to Bryan , or what ?
Don 't rave .
How 's my boy ?
What are you doing ? Who 's this ?
Gross !
Here I 'm ready , little bitch .
You fool , Agu !
What 's the matter with you , mate , they 're my family !
Caco took them , asshole !
Caco is already dead , Brian .
That bastard .
We killed him .
Don 't rave .
Yes , she killed him .
Shit !
You sent a female to do your job , Shine ?
In my band
females are more bastards than your little queers , asshole .
They 'll look for you all , Shine .
Chino and the other Guascas .
If you killed Caco
they are going to kill you .
They are going to kill you all .
We are going to hide .
Yeah , great , yeah .
Where ?
Hey ?
Great Morro . A + .
At one , two , and three .
C 'mon ! C 'mon , Tucsy .
Wow , it 's like the Boingland ( inflatables park ) of the dark-skinned kids .
- It 's fucking great ! - Don 't rave .
Look , look .
What happened to these ?
They left their fish tank .
Cool .
Look , that one looks like dear Morro .
That one , we 'll name it Estrella .
That one is Shine .
Hey , Pop , it 's like your zoo , but of pure fish .
If there is a zoo , there is a soccer field . C 'mon !
Run , Morro !
Soccer field ... Don 't talk nosense .
Estrella .
Come .
They come for you .
Go get all of them .
Shine .
It would have been me who would have killed him .
- No . - Hello ?
Where are you , fucking sons of a bitch ?
You killed my brother , you bastards !
That fucking girl killed him !
I 'm going to find you , you bastards , if you don 't return that fucking phone !
Fucking Brian .
What do you keep that for ?
That 's the only picture I have of my mom .
Caco took it when he took her away .
- Shine ! - Shine !
What 's up ?
We did not find a court but we found this .
All right . Let the four fit here .
C 'mon , mate .
It looks like a " Y " , mate .
Now I 'm going to write the name .
This is Chichorito .
Don 't worry , Morro , it will last only a month .
Let 's see , lend me your ball .
It looks like Caco .
Here .
Kittens ? Don 't rave , you bastard .
They are tigers . It 's for her protection .
Let 's see how yours turned out , Morro .
What happened to him ?
He fell .
I 'm going to fix it for you .
You must be careful because it stings and you 'll bleed . Right ?
Don 't cry anymore .
Yes ? Look , that 's it .
Why do you have wishes ?
Put that light out , you bastards .
Let us sleep .
These fish are like the tiger .
They escaped from their cage .
Poor tiger .
He had a house ,
a mom ,
in the jungle
and now he 's alone .
He 's afraid .
No .
He has already gone through all the bad things ,
and wanders wherever he wants .
He 's the king of all this fucking kingdom .
Tigers are not afraid .
Did you find your mom in the photos ?
Don 't you have pictures of her ?
They stayed in the house .
Mine also stayed in the house and burned down .
Did they burn your house ?
They threw gasoline and ...
they threw this .
They grabbed my mom
when we were leaving .
What are you going to spend your last wish on ?
I can 't ask for your mom to come back .
But could you ask that ...
this burnt goes off ?
- No . - Then I 'll bring you the photos from your house .
No .
Every time I make a wish
it comes out very wrong .
How can a wish come out ... ?
Now , fucking brat !
Where is that fucking phone ?
Where is it , you bastard ?
Where is it ? Tell me . Does that fucking girl who killed my brother have it ?
You will take her to me , son of a bitch .
Next one .
And what 's your name ?
Rapop .
And what is your specialty ?
- I do rap . - Let 's see . Show us .
Where 's Shine ?
I don 't know . But , do you want to be a star ?
Okay .
Heck . My lights went out .
It 's ugly , no , horrible . Terrible !
Mate , get off .
- I know where he lives . - I don 't think so .
Next one .
Yes , Chino , I swear that now we 'll bring it to you .
Estrella .
They come for you .
I 'm leading you
to where we dead
are waiting for him .
Where is my fucking phone ? I 'll take you to where they 'll soften you up , bitch .
Estrella !
Son of a bitch ! Kill that bastard !
No !
Let 's move !
And why do they want this phone ?
It must have something in .
Let 's see .
Take it off .
Take it off !
Are you recording , you bastard ?
It 's Chino .
Caco recorded it to fuck him .
Look for Chino .
Dial him .
What do you want me to dial him for ?
You have something I need .
You have to return it to me .
Or I 'll go look for it .
And I will find it .
We are going to give it to you .
When ?
When you disappear the Guascas .
Tomorrow at seven in the morning .
Where ?
There are some toilets on the road , in front of La Tonina .
You come and give me that phone ,
and right there the Guascas will be finished .
Or you don 't come , but then I 'll go find you ,
and I 'll find you ,
and I 'm going to do you the same thing I did to Caco .
Because you didn 't kill him , right ?
Although you 're telling everyone that you did .
I killed him , cowgirl , for not giving me that fucking phone .
Think about it .
Liar .
You said you killed Caco , but you didn 't .
Look what happened .
Liar . Take care of Morro .
There you go , dear Morro .
Another dead
because of him .
Here we are , all of us .
Bring him .
Shine !
Wasn 't he in the truck station ?
You shit your pants .
No , I knew where he was .
Shut up .
What do you want ?
Shine , can you lend me a phone ?
- What do you want it for ? - I want to make a call .
No , the other one . We don 't even have the password for this one .
And besides , who are you going to talk to , mate ?
Don 't ! Pop !
Pop , come here !
Come here !
Bring him
where he put us all .
Bring him to us .
Tigers are not afraid . Tigers are not afraid . Tigers are not afraid .
No , not in my life . The police are the worst .
- No , let 's see if they can help us . - No , they are not going to help us .
So give me that phone , mate . Give me that phone .
Stop it , Shine .
Here there 's a video of that fucking Chino killing someone .
- And who chases the thugs ? - I don 't know , but the police does not .
So give me that phone .
- Come here . - Let go of me !
Come here , you bastards !
Police !
What 's up ? - We come to make a complaint .
This is a crime against humanity .
Look .
Where did you get that ?
Do you know who does it belong to ?
Let 's go , you bastard .
Don 't ! Why ?
You can not leave !
- Why ? - Don 't !
Don 't !
Sons of bitches !
Bastards .
Couple of assholes , both of you .
What did I tell you ?
Give me the phone , mate . And you give me the other one .
What was your idea ? That Chino kill us ?
That Chino kill us ?
Shut up , you bastard .
You always have all the ideas , don 't you ?
Yes , then shut up .
Where are you going ?
We have to look for Estrella . I have to tell her something .
Wait !
Estrella !
He left dear Morro alone .
What a bastard !
Poor thing , he must be cold .
We can not leave him here .
- First we have to go ... - First Morro .
Help me cover him .
Cover him .
Help me .
He 's stiff .
That does not matter , that 's normal . C 'mon .
And where are we going to put him ?
They are burying me .
I 'm cold .
Where ?
Everywhere .
No , where are you being buried ?
Oh .
Wait , stop the fridge , mate .
How did you find us ?
Dear Morro told me .
Now he even talks ?
Morro is here , saved ,
after you abandoned him .
You asshole .
And liar .
Asshole liar .
I have to tell you something .
The video we saw ...
Oh , later .
We have to go see Chino
else they will come to kill us all .
First Morro .
Help me .
Rest in peace .
Maxwell Alexander Aureliano Villarreal Mora VÃ ¡ zquez .
Mora VÃ ¡ zquez .
Are we going to go to Chino ?
We have to go .
Estrella !
Lend it to me .
Death is going to take us .
Shut up , you bastard . Don 't talk with your face painted like that .
It 's our war camouflage .
Great . Chino will say :
" Don 't touch them , they painted themselves with dry pen . "
" They must be dangerous . "
Assholes .
- C 'mon , remove that . - But with what ?
Well , with drool , asshole .
C 'mon .
Estrella .
The lady we saw is ...
What if I use my third wish to disappear Chino ?
But what if it goes wrong ?
There are no wishes .
There is nothing .
There are no tigers .
We are the only things there is .
BATHROOMS
Seems those fucking toddlers are not coming .
Do you want us to go get them ?
Son of the bitch .
I 'm not going to vote for him .
- Let go of me , you bastard . - Tio , let him alone . Let him free .
Where is my phone ?
What 's the password ?
It 's that one , boss , it has the dragon of Caco .
Now can we kill them ?
No !
Chino , Chino ...
No , Chino !
We had a deal , right ?
Get out of here .
I don 't want to see you again .
Where is my mom ?
How the fuck will I know ?
Go .
They killed my mom here , right ?
Shine .
I need to know .
We have to go .
I changed the phone . He 's going to realize .
What do you do ?
There are no wishes .
Don 't rave .
I wish your scar removed .
You see ? There are no wishes .
Shine . Shine !
Shine .
When you dialed , it did not have a password . Right , you bastard ?
Where are you , fucking brat ?
Come out !
Where are you ?
I 'm going to kill you , you bastard !
Where are you ? I 'm going to kill you , asshole .
I 'm going to eat your tongue , you bastard !
I saw you , bitch .
Mom .
I 'm going to kill you , you bastard !
I saw you , asshole .
Let me out , asshole ! Let me out , you bastard !
Goodbye , cowboy .
Goodbye .
Tigers are not afraid .
They have already gone through all the bad things
and they came out the other side .
They are kings
of this kingdom of broken things .
Because we have to remember :
we are princes ,
we are warriors
and tigers ,
and tigers are not afraid .